{
    "id": "574ada28492b496a9e12637e1e6cbc75",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The village ................................ I was born is a few hundred miles from here.",
            "description": "Where can mean in which.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the store in ................................ I used to work.",
            "description": "In which is similar to where. We cannot use that after a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was admired by the people with ............................... he worked.",
            "description": "In a formal style, the preposition comes before the relative pronoun. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He was loved by the people ................................. he worked with.",
            "description": "In an informal style, the preposition goes at the end of the sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house in .................................... I was born.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the room .................................... I was born in.",
            "description": "That is used when the preposition goes at the end. It cannot be used after a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't know ................................. she is from.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know ................................ country she is from?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He always quarreled with the people with ................................... he worked.",
            "description": "We cannot use who and that after prepositions.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know …………………………. I met at the club yesterday?",
            "description": "In an informal style who is also possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. she said made me angry.",
            "description": "What means the things which.",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "That",
                "Which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You should give me …………………………. I want.",
            "description": "What means the things which.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}